Guide to the Cornell University Libraries Acquisitions Dept. correspondence, 1959-1984.
Cornell University Libraries Aquisitions Dept. correspondence, 1959-1984
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Libraries Acquisitions Dept. correspondence, 1959-1984.
13-3-1086
Cornell University. Libraries. Acquisitions Dept.
42.6 cubic ft.
Correspondence, bulletins, memos, meeting minutes, reports, budget books.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence files dealing with requests for books as well as cancellations of request, and letters denoting request or shipment errors. Also included are information bulletins, technical memos, minutes of library department meetings, the 1964-65 Book Budget, a Catalogue Procedures Manual, and payroll carbons from the Industrial and Labor Relations library. 1963-1964 monthly reports, sample acquisition forms, and special non-heading orders are also included.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence files dealing with requests for books as well as cancellations of request, and letters denoting request or shipment errors. Also included are information bulletins, technical memos, minutes of library department meetings, the 1964-65 Book Budget, a Catalogue Procedures Manual, and payroll carbons from the Industrial and Labor Relations library. 1963-64 monthly reports, sample acquisition forms, and special non-heading orders are also included.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.Libraries. Acquisitions Dept.; Cornell University--Libraries.
Subjects:
Acquisitions (Libraries)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Edward G. Allen and Sons, Nov. 1963-June 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Edward G. Allen and Sons, July 1964-Dec. 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A.L.A. Reprinting Committee (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A (a-l) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A (m-z) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The Baker and Taylor Co. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Blunk, Dr. Hans (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Book Budget, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- B (a-l) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- B (m-roc) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bro-Dart Books, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- B (roe-z) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Catalogue Procedures Manual (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Collier-MacMillan Co. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Cornell University Library Information Bulletin (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Cornell University Library Technical Memos (Box 1, Folder 16)
- C (a-l) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- C (m-z) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Department Heads Meetings (Box 1, Folder 19)
- D (a-l) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- D (m-z) (Box 1, Folder 21)
- E (a-l) (Box 1, Folder 22)
- E (m-z) (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Fine Arts Library - 282 Special (Box 1, Folder 24)
- F (a-l) (Box 1, Folder 25)
- F (m-z) (Box 1, Folder 26)
- G (a-l) (Box 1, Folder 27)
- G (m-z) (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Harrassowitz, Jan. 1964-June 1964 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Harrassowitz, July 1964-Dec. 1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Harvard University (Box 1, Folder 31)
- H (a-l) (Box 1, Folder 32)
- H (m-z) (Box 1, Folder 33)
- ILR Payroll Carbons (Box 1, Folder 34)
- I (a-l) (Box 1, Folder 35)
- I (m-z) (Box 1, Folder 36)
- J (a-l) (Box 1, Folder 37)
- J (m-z) (Box 1, Folder 38)
- K (a-l) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- K (m-z) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Library of Congress (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- L (a-l) (Box 2, Folder 6)
- L (m-z) (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Dr. McCarthy (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Makely's (Box 2, Folder 9)
- McGraw-Hill Books (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Monthly Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- M (a-l) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- M (m-z) (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Martinus Nijhoff (Box 2, Folder 14)
- N (a-l) (Box 2, Folder 15)
- N (m-z) (Box 2, Folder 16)
- O (a-l) (Box 2, Folder 17)
- O (m-z) (Box 2, Folder 18)
- P (a-l) (Box 2, Folder 19)
- P (m-z) (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Prentice-Hall (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Q (a-z) (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Rochester Exchange (Box 2, Folder 23)
- R (a-l) (Box 2, Folder 24)
- R (m-z) (Box 2, Folder 25)
- S (a-l) (Box 2, Folder 26)
- S (m-z) (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Sample Acquisitions Forms (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Special Non-heading Orders (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Steehert-Hafner (Box 2, Folder 30)
- T (a-l) (Box 2, Folder 31)
- T (m-z) (Box 2, Folder 32)
- University Microfilms (Box 2, Folder 33)
- U (a-z) (Box 2, Folder 34)
- V (a-z) (Box 2, Folder 35)
- W (a-z) (Box 2, Folder 36)
- X-Y-Z (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Acquisitions Fund Numbers, 1960 (Box 3)
- Acquisitions Department - What It Is and What It Does, 1960 (Box 3)
- Edward G. Allen and Son, 1960 (Box 3)
- Annual Report, 1960 (Box 3)
- A (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- Baker and Taylor Co., 1960 (Box 3)
- B (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- Cornell University Library Information Bulletin, 1960 (Box 3)
- Cornell University Library Technical Memos, 1960 (Box 3)
- C (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- Department Heads Meeting, 1960 (Box 3)
- D (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- Egypt, 1960 (Box 3)
- Dr. McCarthy Egyptian, 1960 (Box 3)
- Entomology, Periodicals, 1960 (Box 3)
- E (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Folder, 1959-1960 (Box 3)
- Fiske Icelandic Collection, 1960 (Box 3)
- F (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- G (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- Otto Harrassowitz, 1960 (Box 3)
- H (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- I (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- J (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- K (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- Library of Congress, 1960 (Box 3)
- Dr. McCarthy, 1960 (Box 3)
- McGraw-Hill Book Co., 1960 (Box 3)
- Microfilm Orders, 1960 (Box 3)
- M (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- Martin Nijhoff, 1960 (Box 3)
- School of Nutrition, 1960 (Box 3)
- N (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- Order - Request Forms Instructions, 1960 (Box 3)
- O (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- Periodicals List, 1960 (Box 3)
- Periodicals List - Completed, 1960 (Box 3)
- Personnel Job Descriptions, 1960 (Box 3)
- P (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- Reprint Expediting Service, 1960 (Box 3)
- R (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- S (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- T (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- U (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- V (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- W (a-z), 1960 (Box 3)
- X-Y-Z, 1960 (Box 3)
- Edward G. Allen and Son, 1961 (Box 4)
- A (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- Book Budget, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
- B (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- Cornell University Library Personnel, 1961 (Box 4)
- Cornell University Library Technical Memos, 1961 (Box 4)
- C (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- Department Heads Meetings, 1961 (Box 4)
- D (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- E (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- Fiscal Folder, 1960-1961 (Box 4)
- Flower Veterinary Periodical List, 1961 (Box 4)
- F (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- G (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- Otto Harrassowitz, 1961 (Box 4)
- H (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- International Congress of the History of Science - Xth, 1961 (Box 4)
- I (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- J (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- K (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- Library of Congress, 1961 (Box 4)
- L (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- Dr. McCarthy, 1961 (Box 4)
- McGraw-Hill Book Co., 1961 (Box 4)
- M (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- NDEA Reconciliation, 1961 (Box 4)
- Nijhoff, 1961 (Box 4)
- N (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- O (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- P (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- Q (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- R (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- Seven Gables, 1961 (Box 4)
- S (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- T (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- U (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- V (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- W (a-z), 1961 (Box 4)
- Zoology Library, 1961 (Box 4)
- X-Y-Z, 1961 (Box 4)
- A (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- Baker and Taylor, 1962 (Box 5)
- B (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- Cornell University Libraries - Technical Memos, 1962 (Box 5)
- C (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- Department Heads Meetings, 1962 (Box 5)
- D (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- E (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- Fine Arts Library - 282 Special, 1962 (Box 5)
- F (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- G (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- Otto Harrassowitz, 1962 (Box 5)
- Harvard University, 1962 (Box 5)
- H (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- I (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- J (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- K (a-l), 1962 (Box 5)
- Library of Congress, 1962 (Box 5)
- L (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- McGraw-Hill, 1962 (Box 5)
- M (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- Dr. McCarthy, 1962 (Box 5)
- Martinus Nijhoff, 1962 (Box 5)
- N (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- O (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- Prentice Hall, 1962 (Box 5)
- P (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- Q (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- R (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- S (a-l), 1962 (Box 5)
- S (m-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- T (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- University Microfilms, 1962 (Box 5)
- U (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- V (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- W (a-z), 1962 (Box 5)
- X-Y-Z, 1962 (Box 5)
- Zoology Library, 1962 (Box 5)
- Richard Abel Co., 1971 (Box 5)
- Abel (Returns Only), 1971 (Box 5)
- Edward G. Allen and Son, Ltd., 1971 (Box 5)
- American..., 1971 (Box 5)
- Automation, 1971 (Box 5)
- A (a-l), 1971 (Box 5)
- A (m-z), 1971 (Box 5)
- B (a-l), 1971 (Box 5)
- B (m-z), 1971 (Box 5)
- Marcel Blancheteau, 1971 (Box 5)
- Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
- University of California, 1971 (Box 5)
- Cambridge University, 1971 (Box 5)
- CUL Technical Memos, 1971 (Box 5)
- Cowan-Algiers Project, 1971 (Box 5)
- C (a-z), 1971 (Box 5)
- D (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- E (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- F.A.U.L. - masfile, 1971 (Box 6)
- Four Continent Book Corp., 1971 (Box 6)
- Funds, 1971 (Box 6)
- F (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- G (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- G.K. Hall and Co., 1971 (Box 6)
- Harrassowitz, 1971 (Box 6)
- Harvard University, 1971 (Box 6)
- Helbing and Lichtenhahn, 1971 (Box 6)
- H (a-l), 1971 (Box 6)
- H (m-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- IDC, NUC, 1971 (Box 6)
- I (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- J (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- K (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- Sous La Lampe, 1971 (Box 6)
- Library Bookseller, 1971 (Box 6)
- Library of Congress, 1971 (Box 6)
- L (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- Makeley's, 1971 (Box 6)
- Makeley's, 1971 (Box 6)
- M.I.T. (Mass. Inst. of Technology), 1971 (Box 6)
- McGraw-Hill, 1971 (Box 6)
- Morgan Editeur Siege Social, 1971 (Box 6)
- M (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- Nardecchia, 1971 (Box 6)
- Nijhoff, 1971 (Box 6)
- N.P.A.C., 1971 (Box 6)
- N (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- O (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- Prentice-Hall, 1971 (Box 6)
- P (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- Q (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- Random House - Singer School Division, 1971 (Box 6)
- R (a-l), 1971 (Box 6)
- R (m-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- Statistics, 1971 (Box 6)
- Stechert-Hafner, 1971 (Box 6)
- S (a-l), 1971 (Box 6)
- S (m-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- Taylor-Carlisle, 1971 (Box 6)
- T (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- University of Michigan, 1971 (Box 6)
- U (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- V (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- John Wiley and Sons, 1971 (Box 6)
- W (a-z), 1971 (Box 6)
- X-Y-Z, 1971 (Box 6)
- Edward G. Allen and Son, Ltd., 1967 (Box 7)
- American Express Company, 1967 (Box 7)
- Automation, 1967 (Box 7)
- A (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- Budget Proposal, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
- B (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- Cornell University Library Technical Memos, 1967 (Box 7)
- C (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- D (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- E (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- F (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- G (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- Otto Harrassowitz, 1967 (Box 7)
- H (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- I-J-K, 1967 (Box 7)
- L (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- Monthly Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
- M (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- National Program for Acquisitions and Cataloging (NPAC), 1967 (Box 7)
- N (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- O (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- P (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- Q (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- R (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- Stechert-Hafner, 1967 (Box 7)
- S (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- T (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- University Microfilms Ltd., 1967 (Box 7)
- V (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- W (a-z), 1967 (Box 7)
- X-Y-Z, 1967 (Box 7)
- American Express Company, 1968 (Box 7)
- Automation, 1968 (Box 7)
- A (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- Marcel Blancheteau, 1968 (Box 7)
- Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
- B (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- C (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- D (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- E (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- F (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- G (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- Otto Harrassowitz, 1968 (Box 7)
- H (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- I, (no J), K, 1968 (Box 7)
- L (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- M (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- National Program for Acquisitions and Cataloging (NAPAC), 1968 (Box 7)
- N (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- O (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- Pandit University of Delhi (J. Kelley), 1968 (Box 7)
- P (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- Q (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- R (a-l), 1968 (Box 7)
- R (m-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- South Central Research Library Council, 1968 (Box 7)
- Statistics, 1968 (Box 7)
- Stechert-Hafner, 1968 (Box 7)
- S (a-l), 1968 (Box 7)
- S (m-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- Tiffler, Rene Steinberg Fund, 1968 (Box 7)
- T (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- University Microfilms Ltd., 1968 (Box 7)
- U (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- V (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- W (a-z), 1968 (Box 7)
- X-Y-Z, 1968 (Box 7)
- Africana Studies, 1969 (Box 8)
- Edward G. Allen, 1969 (Box 8)
- American Express, 1969 (Box 8)
- American..., 1969 (Box 8)
- Arabic Languages, 1969 (Box 8)
- Automation..., 1969 (Box 8)
- A (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- Baker and Taylor, 1969 (Box 8)
- Biological Sciences, 1969 (Box 8)
- Marcel Blancheteau, 1969 (Box 8)
- Bookazine, 1969 (Box 8)
- Books for Libraries, 1969 (Box 8)
- Bro-Dart, 1969 (Box 8)
- B (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- University of California, 1969 (Box 8)
- Cambridge University, 1969 (Box 8)
- Center for Research Libraries, 1969 (Box 8)
- CUL Technical Memos, 1969 (Box 8)
- Cowan-Algiers Project (Linguistics Dept.), 1969 (Box 8)
- C (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- D (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- E (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- F.A.U.L. - masfile, 1969 (Box 8)
- F (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- Greenwood Press, 1969 (Box 8)
- Gregg International Publ., Gregg Press, 1969 (Box 8)
- G (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- Harrassowitz, Jan. 1969-June 1969 (Box 8)
- Harrassowitz, July 1969-Dec. 1969 (Box 8)
- Harvard University, 1969 (Box 8)
- Helbing and Lichtenhahn, 1969 (Box 8)
- H (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- I (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- J (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- K (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- Latin America, 1969 (Box 8)
- Library of Congress, 1969 (Box 8)
- L (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- McGraw-Hill, Inc., 1969 (Box 8)
- Makely's Inc., 1969 (Box 8)
- Monthly Reports, 1969 (Box 8)
- Morgan Editeur Siege Social, 1969 (Box 8)
- M (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- Nardecchia, 1969 (Box 8)
- Nijhoff, 1969 (Box 8)
- N (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- O (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- P (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- Q (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- R (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- Seeber, 1969 (Box 8)
- Stechert-Hafner, 1969 (Box 8)
- S (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- Taylor-Carlisle, 1969 (Box 8)
- T (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- University Microfilms, 1969 (Box 8)
- V (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- W (a-z), 1969 (Box 8)
- X-Y-Z, 1969 (Box 8)
- Acquisitions Correspondence Files (A-L), Jan. 1, 1974-June 30, 1974 (Box 9)
- Acquisitions Correspondence Files (M-Z), Jan. 1, 1974-June 30, 1974 (Box 10)
- Abel, July 1974-June 1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Abel Returns, July 1974-June 1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Edward G. Allen and Son, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- A Miscellaneous (a-l), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- American, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- A Miscellaneous (m-z), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Baker and Taylor, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Baker and Taylor Returns, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Blackwell's, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Blancheteau, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- B Miscellaneous (a-l), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Ballen, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- B Miscellaneous (m-z), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- CUL Bulletin, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- CUL Technical Memos, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- CUL Weekly Gazette, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- C Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- C Miscellaneous (a-l), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- C Miscellaneous (m-z), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- John Cotts Library Service, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Customs, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- D Miscellaneous (a-l), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- D Miscellaneous (m-z), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- E Miscellaneous (a-l), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- E Miscellaneous (m-z), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Four Continents, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Funds, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- F Miscellaneous (a-l), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- F Miscellaneous (m-z), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- G Miscellaneous (a-l), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- G Miscellaneous (m-z), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- G.K. Hall, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Harrassowitz, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Harvard, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- H Miscellaneous (a-l), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- H Miscellaneous (m-z), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- I Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- International, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Walter J. Johnson, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- J Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Johns Hopkins, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Kraus (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Kubon and Sagner (Box 12, Folder 2)
- K Miscellaneous (a-l) (Box 12, Folder 3)
- K Miscellaneous (m-z) (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Library Bookseller (TAAB) (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Library of Congress (Box 12, Folder 6)
- L Miscellaneous (a-l) (Box 12, Folder 7)
- L Miscellaneous (m-z) (Box 12, Folder 8)
- McGraw-Hill (Box 12, Folder 9)
- M Miscellaneous (a-l) (Box 12, Folder 10)
- M Miscellaneous (m-z) (Box 12, Folder 11)
- N Miscellaneous (a-l) (Box 12, Folder 12)
- N Miscellaneous (m-z) (Box 12, Folder 13)
- O Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Prentice-Hall (Box 12, Folder 15)
- P Miscellaneous (a-l) (Box 12, Folder 16)
- P Miscellaneous (m-z) (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Q Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 18)
- R Miscellaneous (a-l) (Box 12, Folder 19)
- R Miscellaneous (m-z) (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Supplies, Orders (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Supplies, Orders (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Supplies, Orders (Box 12, Folder 23)
- S Miscellaneous (a-l) (Box 12, Folder 24)
- S Miscellaneous (m-z) (Box 12, Folder 25)
- T Miscellaneous (a-l) (Box 12, Folder 26)
- T Miscellaneous(m-z) (Box 12, Folder 27)
- U Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 28)
- V Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Wiley and SOns (Box 12, Folder 30)
- W Miscellaneous (a-l) (Box 12, Folder 31)
- W Miscellaneous (m-z) (Box 12, Folder 32)
- X-Y-Z Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Searching, Monthly Statistics, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Searching, Monthly Statistics, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Searching, Monthly Statistics, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Statistical Reports, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Edward G. Allen and Son, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- A Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- A Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- American, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Ballen, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Baker and Taylor, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Blackwell's, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Blancheteau, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- B Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Customs, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- CUL Weekly Gazette, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- C Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- C Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- John Coutts Library Service, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- CUL Technical Memos, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Doubleday and Company, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- D Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- D Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- E Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- E Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Four Continents, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- F Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- F Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- G Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- G Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- G.K. Hall, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Harrassowitz, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Harvard, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- H Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- I Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- I Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Walter J. Johnson, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- J Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- J Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Kraus, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Kubon and Sagner, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- K Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- K Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Library Bookseller (TAAB), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Library of Congress, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- L Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- L Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- McGraw-Hill, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- M Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- M Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- N Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- N Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- O Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- O Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- P Miscellaneous (a-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Prentice-Hall, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- P Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Q Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- R Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- R Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Statistical Reports, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 27-29)
- Supplies, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- S Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- S Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- T Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- T Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- U Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- V Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Wiley and Sons, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- W Miscellaneous (a-l), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- W Miscellaneous (m-z), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- X-Y-Z Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 1963 (Box 15)
- Corespondence (A-E), 1972 (Box 16)
- Correspondence (F-R), 1972 (Box 17)
- Correspondence (S-Z), 1972 (Box 18)
- Correspondence (A-H), 1965 (Box 19)
- Correspondence (I-Z), 1965 (Box 20)
- Correspondence (A-L), 1973 (Box 21)
- Correspondence (M-Z), 1973 (Box 22)
- Correspondence (A-M), 1970 (Box 23)
- Correspondence (N-Z), 1970 (Box 24)
- Correspondence (A-D), 1966 (Box 25)
- Correspondence (E-Z), 1966 (Box 26)
- Russian Bibliography Correspondence, 1962-1968? (Box 27)
- Exchange Correspondence, 1966 (Box 28)
- Exchange Correspondence, 1945-? (Box 29)
- Gifts and Exchange Correspondence, 1958-? (Box 30)
- PL-480 Correspondence and Corporate Donors File, 1970-1971; 1976-1977 (Box 31)
- Acquisitions Correspondence Files (A-I), July 1, 1976-June 30, 1977 (Box 32)
- Acquisitions Correspondence Files (J-Z), July 1, 1976-June 30, 1977 (Box 33)
- Acquisitions Correspondence Files (A-L), July 1, 1977-June 30, 1978 (Box 34)
- Acquisitions Correspondence Files (M-Z), July 1, 1977-June 30, 1978 (Box 35)
- Acquisitions Correspondence Files, Jan. 1959-Dec. 1960 (Box 36)
- Correspondence (A-M), 1978-1979 (Box 37)
- Correspondence (N-Z), 1978-1979 (Box 38)
- Bowe Collection (from CMB), 197 (Box 38)
- OCLC (from CMB), 197 (Box 38)
- Correspondence (A-L), 1979-1980 (Box 39)
- Correspondence (M-Z), 1979-1980 (Box 40)
- (A-Z), July 1980-June 1981 (Box 41)
- (A-F), July 1981-June 1982 (Box 41)
- (G-Z), July 1981-June 1982 (Box 42)
- (A-Z), July 1982-June 1983 (Box 42)
- Copying Machines (Box 43)
- Deposit Accounts (Box 43)
- EBS Book Service (Box 43)
- Encumberances - Historical (Box 43)
- Library Automation (Box 43)
- Job Descriptions - Outdated (Box 43)
- A-Z, July 1, 1983-June 30, 1984 (Box 44)